

I am a software development professional with 14 years of experience in web systems, both backend and frontend. Currently my focus is directed to the frontend in Javascript with the React and Vue frameworks, and the management of various tools applied in the different stages of development, from its beginning to its publication.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+57 3212684453

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carloscamacho-29755043/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/carloscgo

EMAIL:

carloscgo123@gmail.com

CARLOS CAMACHO

Sr. Fullstack

EDUCATION

Higher University Technician in Computer Science

February 1999 - June 2004

EXPERIENCE

Mercury Cash - Sr. Fullstack

February 2018 – October 2022

Senior Backend Developer (PHP Laravel), Project Leader and Senior Frontend (VueJs & ReactJs). Coordinate platform migrations from Laravel to VueJs and later to ReactJs.

Empresa Inteligente Asociados - Web and Mobile Developer

October 2017 – February 2018

Backend developer PHP Codelgniter (Rest API), Frontend jQuery and Bootstrap, and Mobile with Ionic, Angular. MySQL DB administrator.

Grupo Adames, Drink2Go – Web Developer

October 2017 - February 2018

PHP Laravel developer, jQuery Frontend and Bootstrap. MySQL DB Administrator.

Net Sistem C.A – Director of Development and Web Developer

October 2009 - March 2017

PHP Developer, Frontend jQuery and Bootstrap, MySQL and PostgreSQL DB Administrator (Stored Procedure, Triggers, Events, View).

DHD Soluciones C.A - Web Developer

February 2006 - October 2009

Programmer Analyst, Developer of web pages and systems with PHP and Javascript. Promoted as project leader 3 months into the contract.

SKILLS

